Merve Coskun

Junior Full Stack Developer

merve coskun2013@hotmail.com | +46 (0)70 812 64 33 | Lund - SWEDEN

LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/merve-coskun-fullstack/
GitHub https://github.com/mervecoskunn?tab=repositories

Executive Summary

Junior Software Developer with a Diploma in Full Stack Software Development from the Code Institute. The Diploma course is a 5-project course building my own portfolio using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Python and using useful frameworks.

I have 4 years' experience in Economy as a personal costumer representative in the bank. I am fast learner, good team-member and a good player with strong communication skills that can help solve any problems that may arise.

Education

Sep 2023 – Jun 2024 Diploma in Full Stack Software Development

Code Institute – Dublin, IRELAND

(Credit Rated by University of West of Scotland)

Mar 2023 - May 2023 Web Development - 1

KOMVUX (NTI-Skolan) - Varberg, SWEDEN

KOMVUX (NTI-Skolan) - Varberg, SWEDEN

Sep 2005 – Jun 2011 Bachelor of Economics

Selcuk University – Konya, TURKEY

Technical Skillset

Technologies: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Python Frameworks: Django, jQuery, Bootstrap, ReactJS

Version Control: Git, GitHub

Portfolio Projects

1. Swedish Courses - A website that announces Swedish courses and detailed information organized by a Swedish private company for its employees.

Technologies Used - HTML5 · CSS3 · GitHub · Responsive Web Design **GitHub** - https://github.com/mervecoskunn/swedishcourses

2. Web Quiz – It is a quiz project where users can test their HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript skills and send feedback.

Technologies Used - HTML5 - CSS - JavaScript **GitHub** - https://github.com/mervecoskunn/Web-Quiz

3. Freya Photos - It is a website project that allows a photographer to communicate with customers and tries to reach new customers by referencing her previous work.

Technologies Used - HTML5 · CSS3 - WordPress

GitHub - https://github.com/mervecoskunn/Freya-Photo-Website

WordPress - https://freyaphoto3.wordpress.com/

Work Experience

Jun 2021 – Feb 2023 Career Transition / Break

Varberg, SWEDEN

- Decided for career transition.
- Started with C#, Html5, Css3, Bootstrap, JavaScript, React and still getting professional private education.

Sep 2013 – Feb 2014 Personal Banking Representative

HSBC Private Banking Istanbul, Turkey

- To provide information to our bank's customers in my portfolio in the field they need, to explain investment instruments and to offer them the most suitable investment instrument.
- Assisting in all kinds of nursing operations.
- To carry out transactions in personal, housing and vehicle loans and to inform the customer about this.

Mar 2012 – Aug 2013 Bank Teller

Turkiye Finans Bank Istanbul, Turkey

- Provides account services to customers by receiving deposits and loan payments; cashing checks; issuing savings withdrawals; recording night and mail deposits; selling cashier's checks, traveller's checks, and series e bonds; answering questions in person or on telephone; referring to other bank services.
- Records transactions by logging cashier's checks, traveller's checks, and other special services; preparing currency transaction reports.
- Cross-sells bank products by answering inquiries; informing customers of new services and product promotions; ascertaining customers' needs; directing customers to a branch representative.

Certifications

- META Introduction to Front End Development
- CODER Informatics Academy ReactJS
- CODER Informatics Academy JavaScript
- CODER Informatics Academy Web Design
- Udemy HTML5 and CSS3
- KOMVUX (NTI-Skolan) English as Second Language (Advance Level)
- KOMVUX (NTI-Skolan) Swedish as Second Language (Advance Level)

Interests / Additional Information

- I attend regular 'women in tech' networking events.
- Volunteering and community involvement.
- Travelling and discovering the cross-nation cultures.
- Fluent Turkish, Advance English, Advance Swedish.
- Facilitator of family events and activities.